

# Mateusz Lota Junior Tester



Poland, Łódź



mateuszlota112@gmail.com



+48 510 817 777

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/mateusz-lota

GitHub: github.com/MateuszLota

## SUMMARY:

I have a great desire and motivation to start a new role in Testing industry. Thanks to technical education and past experience, I have the skills of being meticulous and inquisitive. Creating diffrent types of tests are not a problem.

I am good at multi-tasking as well as when it comes to time management skills.

I'm fond of mountain biking and martial arts, I take part in amateur competitions. Reaching my goal despite any difficulties, I like learning new things and developing my skills, both personal and professional.

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realizing the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation). I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purposes necessary for the recruitment process (in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws of 2018, item 1000) and in accordance with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the

## WORK EXPERIENCE:

#### TESTER INTERN

Philips | Nov 2022 - Apr 2023

- · Working with international clients.
- Creating tests scenerios and giving reports from it.
- · Making integrations and system tests
  - Solving urgent problems.

#### WORK&TRAVEL USA

May 2022 - Oct 2022

- Working with international clients.
- Creating plans and giving reports from it.
- Helping with configurations of computer systems
- Solving urgent problems.

#### IT SUPPORT

KONCEPT SYSTEMY INFORMATYCZNE S.C. | Oct 2022 - Apr 2022

- · Remote users support.
- Installation and configuration of operating systems.
- · Configuration of routers and servers.
- · Solving urgent problems.

#### CUSTOMER SERVICE

DECATHLON | Sept 2021 - Nov 2022

- · Assembling and repairing bikes.
- · Customer service and advice.
- Maintaining a clean workplace.
- Solving urgent

## **EDUCATION:**

#### ISTQB FL Certyficate

June 2023

Coders Lab | Manual Tester

UDEMY | Fundamentals of manual software testing Course

Jan 2023

Credential URL: Certificate Link

## GEODETIC AND TECHNICAL SCHOOLS IN LODZ:

Vocational secondary school | 2017 - 2021

- · IT technician
- EE08 Certificate (Installation and operation of computer systems, peripherals and networks)
- EE09 Certificate (Programming, development and administration of websites and databases)

### MAIN SKILLS:

- . Basic of: HTML, CSS, SQL
- · Basic of: Jmeter
- · Basic of: Postman, API
- Agile, SCRUM, Canban
- Qtest, TestLink, Jira
- ISTOB knowledge
- · Creating test cases and test scenarios
- · Making test plans
- Spanish A1
- English B2/C1